

# **YVES LARDENOIJE**

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth: 03-09-1997

Address: Cederlaan 60, 5616SC Eindhoven

Phone number: +31 6 48576839 **E-mail:** yveslardenoije@gmail.com

**LinkedIn:** Yves Lardenoije

0000

0000

0000

0000

0000

# **CHARACTERISTICS**

Motivated

Quick learner

Reliable

Friendly



Visual studio:

Visual studio code:

C++:

Version control (Git):

Mathematics:

Linux:

C:

Scrum:

Unity:

C#:

Simulink:

# **LANGUAGES**

Dutch:

English:

German:

0000

# **INTERESTS**

Music

Python (machine learning)

Mathematics

Problem solving

Archery Archery

#### **INTERNSHIP GOAL**

My goal during this internship is to work on an exciting and challenging project within embedded software. I would really like to dive into a project which requires a lot of determination from me. I would like to gain real-life experiences, namely working in a team and finding out the challenges of a working environment.

It would be really satisfying to solve a real world problem for the company I work for, furthermore it would be very enjoyable for me to learn new techniques and technologies within the field.

# **EDUCATION**

# **ICT and Technology**

02-2018 until present

## Fontys University of applied science

I have finished my foundation course.

As specialization i have done a number of game design courses.

During the minor i have followed a structured embedded systems course.

#### **Teacher in mathematics**

09-2016 until 01-2018

# Fontys University of applied science

I won the national "wiskunde A-Lympiade"

Not finished

# **Applied mathematics**

09-2015 until 08-2016

TU/Eindhoven
Not finished

# Gymnasium: "Physics and technology" & "physics and health"

09-2009 until 11-6-2015

Connect college

Average score 7 out of 10

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **Software intern**

3-2020 - 8-2020

ASML D&E Veldhoven

Learnt to apply Scrum and software development in a professional environment.

#### Mover

3-1-2019 - 30-1-2019

**UTS Elsloo** 

I worked with enthausiasm and had no problem working long days.

#### **Bartender**

06-2015-05-2016

"de Babbelaar" Maasbracht

I had a lot of fun making people happy and making sure the mood was right.

I also learned to deal with pressure and always work with a smile.

#### **Tutor**

2013 - 2015

Connect College Echt

Part time job where I used to motivate people to study and I explained subjects with patience and always made sure to prepare my work.